spellzone.com 2014-11-20

# Spellzone, Privacy Policy

**SPELLZONE PRIVACY POLICY**

This document outlines the Privacy Policy for Spellzone. Effective from 15 July 2013.

**ATTENTION: This privacy policy applies to the entire contents of this website under the domain name[www.spellzone.com](http://www.spellzone.com/) and other Spellzone domains (“Website”). Please read this policy carefully before using this Website. If you do not accept these terms of this policy, please do not use this Website.   
This notice is issued by Spellzone Limited.**  

### Introduction

This privacy policy is specific to the Spellzone website ("Website"). Spellzone Limited ("Spellzone", "we", "us" or "our") is committed to protecting your privacy online while providing a personalised and valuable service. Our policy explains how we will do this. We will review this policy in the light of comments we receive so please check the latest version. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us.

By using the Website, you are accepting the practices described in this statement.

### 1\. What kind of information do we collect and how do we use it?

1.1. When you subscribe to or ask for further information about the Website, we request some personal information. The elements of your Data that we request may include:

  * Name
  * Job title
  * Organisation name
  * Billing addresses
  * E-mail address
  * Telephone number
  * IP address and browser information.

1.2 Personal information submitted in this way is added to our access control database, hosted by a third party hosting company, and to our customer databases at Spellzone’s premises. This information will be updated if you inform us of any changes. 

1.3. Payment details such as credit card information are handled by third party providers such as WorldPay and PayPal and as such, Spellzone do not hold this information on our databases.

1.4. We may use information in our database to send you information about us and our products which we think may be of interest to you, electronically or otherwise. In the case of subscribers, your personal information will also be used to enable us to verify you are a subscriber and to deliver the Website to you.

1.5. We request personal information (such as your name, email address and other contact details) from you when you contact us with subscription management queries, technical problems, to comment on the Website , or when you ask for information about how to use the service.

1.6. Personal information submitted by you via ‘contact us’ email will not be added to our customer database and we request it simply so that we can respond to you about your query. Statistics regarding the types of queries submitted to us may be collated by us in aggregate form so that we can effectively monitor the site and improve levels of service.

1.7. If you have asked for information or subscribed to the Website in the past and no longer use the service and do not wish us to store information about you, please contact us and we will remove your details from our customer database. We need to store information about current subscribers in order to fulfil our contractual requirements to you and in order to deliver the Website to you.

1.8. Unless you have informed us that you do not wish to receive further information about our products, we may send you direct mail.

1.9. You may notify us either in writing, by telephone, or email that you object to being contacted in a particular stated way. If you use more than one email address to communicate with us, please notify us of each email account you use.  

### 2\. When do we share information?

2.1. We do not sell your personal information to others.

2.2. We may share your information to our key suppliers which assist us in making the Website available to you on the Website (e.g. our hosting supplier) but we have agreed with those third parties that they will keep your information secure and not use it for other purposes. 

2.3. If we believe that your use of the Website is unlawful or damaging to others, we reserve the right to disclose the information we have obtained through the Website about you to the extent that it is reasonably necessary in our opinion to prevent, remedy or take action in relation to such conduct. 

2.4. We may also disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply any agreements or licences with you; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Spellzone Limited, our affiliates, our licensors and suppliers and/or our customers. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

2.5. If any part of our business (including those of our affiliates) is sold or integrated with another business, your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers.

### 3\. Use of cookies

3.1. Spellzone uses 'cookies' and other technologies on the Website. The terms and condition governing Spellzone's use of "cookies" and such other technologies on the Website are set out in the Spellzone Cookie Policy.

3.2. By using the Website, you are agreeing to be bound by the terms of our Cookie Policy.

### 4\. Security

4.1. Spellzone has appropriate measures in place to help ensure that our users’ Data is protected against unauthorised access or use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction and accidental loss. Although we make all reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet.

4.2. Your personal information is stored at a data centre managed by our third party hosting company. The data centre managed by our third party hosting company is specifically designed to be physically secure and to admit authorised personnel only, who are contractually bound to keep all of our data confidential.

4.3. Access to our customer databases is only given on a 'need to know basis'.

### 5\. Transfer of Data

5.1. The Internet is a global environment. Using the Internet to collect and process personal Data necessarily involves the transmission of Data on an international basis. The information you provide may be transferred in transit to countries outside the European Economic Area that do not have similar protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this privacy policy. However, we have taken the steps outlined above to try to improve the security of your information.

5.2. When we collect personal information from you on our website, we are in compliance with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor principles as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from the European Union. 

5.3. By using the Website, you consent to these transfers.

### 6\. Updating Your Details

6.1. If any of the information that you have provided to Spellzone changes e.g. if you change your e-mail address, this can be up-dated via your Spellzone login. If in doubt, please let us know the correct details.

### 7\. Governing Law

7.1 You agree that this Privacy Policy shall be exclusively governed in accordance with the laws of and the courts in England and Wales.

### 8\. Changes to this Policy

8.1 This policy is effective from July2013. From time to time we may make changes to this Privacy policy statement to reflect any changes to our privacy practices in accordance with changes in legislation, best practice or website enhancements. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by placing a prominent notice on our website.

### 9\. Access to Data and Contact Info

9.1. You may request a copy of the personal information we hold about you. Please contact: 

Email  
Tel: +44 (0) 333 990 0132

Or in writing to:

Spellzone Limited  
Holme Hill Cottage  
Church Street  
Whixley  
York YO26 8AR  
United Kingdom

_Company Reg. No. 6884807 Registered in England and Wales_

**Thank you for visiting the Spellzone website.**
